[Hanzhou City, 2002]
Stay where you are!
Put that stuff before you.
Put it down.
What are these?
Fake IDs.
Fake IDs?
You make fake IDs,
and you put your address on the ad?
Just to attract business.
A "big" case, huh?
I-It's pretty big.
The room is big,
and there's an big old man.
Fine. Confiscate the stuff
and take the suspect away.
Our jurisdiction is only this big.
You should be glad there is a case.
Would you have come
if I hadn't made it sound serious?
You appear like a retired old man now.
It's time you got out and about.
What kind of people would trick an officer
into a police run?
Excuse me...
Stop! I'm telling you to stop!
Safety first!
Stay down!
How dare you run?
Where's the stuff?
Are you crazy? Jumping from such a height!
Look at this amount.
Are you a drug trafficker?
See?
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
This is what a big case is. Don't move!
[The Punishment]
[Punish those who commit crimes
and make mistakes]
[so as to discipline them,]
[and execute those
who violate the prohibitions]
[so as to terrify would-be violators.]
[Guanzi – On Laws and Standards]
[Episode 20]
Sir.
Ye Tianyou is onto Qiao Defu now.
He's still coming after us.
Isn't the Ganghang Public Security Bureau
about to be established?
How about...
we have Qin Feng transferred there?
Okay.
Thanks then.
[Hanzhou, Binjiang]
Party Secretary Li.
Director Ye, what brings you here?
I'm just here for a meeting.
Wait, Party Secretary Li.
Are there any difficulties
with the project
in the port development zone
and that entrepreneur Qiao Defu?
I've heard
[Li Zheng,
Municipal Party Secretary of Hanzhou]
several groups
are competing fiercely
over this project.
If there are problems,
please let me know in advance,
so I can get prepared.
Who told you all that?
Is anything up in your precinct?
No, no.
What I said is just hearsay.
It's a major project after all.
Lots of people drool over it.
They say all sorts of things.
The port project
is the city's top priority this year.
If any situation comes up,
report it immediately.
Rest assured.
I will.
Don't be concerned.
The City Party Committee will back you up.
Just go ahead and do your best.
Sure, I will.
I'm leaving then, Party Secretary Li.
-Okay.
-Bye.
Ms. Zhang?
You are...
I'm also a law graduate
of Hanzhou University.
In freshman year, I saw your performance
in a debate competition.
It was so brilliant
that it left a deep impression on me.
You were the girl
who came up on stage to give me flowers?
Yes, exactly.
My name is Wen Jiangyan.
Wen Jiangyan...
Are you from Longwan?
Yes.
I heard Longwan Logistics
is prospering these days,
and will soon partner with
Hanzhou Chengjiang Group.
You're really well-informed.
I'm actually here
to review the contract with them.
Let's exchange business cards.
Sure.
Alumni of Hanzhou University
often hold gatherings at my horse ranch.
They're all elites
from various industries.
Come join us
sometime.
I'll definitely pay a visit
when I have time.
I'll contact you later.
Okay.
See you.
See you, Ms. Zhang.
M-Mr. Ye,
I've heard a lot about you.
Mr. Ye.
Which yacht did Uncle Qiao use to
play cards on?
You mean the one frequented by Mr. Qiao,
right?
It happens to be here today.
That's the one.
Is it the biggest yacht you have?
Mr. Ye,
we can customize any size you like.
The delivery time depends on
how soon you need it.
But the cost...
Did I mention anything about cost?
No.
Mr. Ye, how large a yacht would you like?
Mr. Ye,
I think we should
consult with Chairman first.
He can't bring himself to scold you,
but he has no problem yelling at me.
Remember that watch you bought last time?
Why are you taking his side?
Are you my secretary or his?
Don't tell my father every single thing,
okay?
Besides,
though he gets mad, he always
ends up buying me
what I want, doesn't he?
He does.
That one...
I'll take it.
Mr. Ye,
it has been sold.
We can order a same one for you
if you want.
I hate to wait.
Who did you sell it to?
Call him out. I'll talk to him.
Mr. Ye, it's against company policy
to disclose customer information.
I really can't tell you about the buyer.
I understand.
Privacy matters.
I won't give you a hard time then.
I'll just browse around.
Sure, feel free to do so.
If you need anything, just let me know.
You're really good.
I'm impressed.
You seemed quite composed
when you played a spoiled rich kid.
Thank God none of that was true.
Or your father would be infuriated.
Why stare at me?
And why did you laugh just now?
Weren't you afraid that'd give us away?
Seriously,
you did a great job playing a secretary.
Still taking me as a secretary?
I'll have your...
Stay in our roles.
What are those guys doing?
Captain Qin,
I got a finding.
[Grand Paradise]
[No outside drinks;
Thank you for your cooperation]
Shall I take you somewhere for a rest?
[The Louvre]
You're hiding here!
Three drinks await you as punishment!
Come with me!
No, sir, see,
I don't think she's able to drink anymore.
Why not let her take a break?
Who are you?
A friend of hers.
[The Louvre]
Get lost!
Come with me!
Sir, she can barely stand.
Please let her rest a bit.
Gang!
What is it, Mr. Liu?
Anything wrong?
Who's this guy?
[The Louvre]
I only meant to drink with this girl.
Yet this guy kept pushing me off.
I demand an explanation!
Mr. Liu, don't be mad.
Go back to the room and drink.
Leave this trivial matter to me, alright?
You deal with it then!
Don't worry.
I'll pay for all your expenses today.
Okay?
Okay!
He's paying...
It wasn't like that, bro.
I didn't try to...
Who are you calling "bro"?
Listen up,
everyone's livelihood in Longwan
depends on me.
All your fellows should respect me
like I'm their father!
Got it?
Scram!
Please don't be mad.
I don't even know him.
Let's go have drinks.
Sing a couple of songs with me.
Let's go!
You're Ding Xiaoshuai, right?
Xiaomei wants to see you.
She has asked you to wait a bit.
[Tidy & Tasty Food Court]
Thanks for the phone charm.
Have you forgotten?
You picked it up for me when we first met.
I've always liked bunnies
since I was a kid.
I longed to keep one as a pet
in childhood,
but my family wouldn't allow it.
I saved up for a long time
to buy this phone charm.
It has kept me company
for quite some time.
If it had really gone missing,
I would've felt lost.
Also, thanks for all your help today.
Don't take to heart
what He Gang said.
However, don't intervene again.
Or they'll make you pay
a steep price for irritating them.
I'm fine.
I just noticed...
you seemed unwell, so...
I've got used to it.
With all this drinking every day,
is your body holding up okay?
My job is to drink with clients.
Only when they're pleased
can I make money.
You think I'm suffering?
But this is my job.
I'm full.
You're a good guy.
But you should understand...
we're from different worlds.
Focus on your job as a courier.
Don't come to me again.
I've paid the bill.
Enjoy your meal.
Hey, Biao,
what's up with you lately?
You've been busy running around.
I've approached a guy
named Qiao Defu.
You must be thinking
that I'm putting my life at stake again
just for some money.
But that's not true.
I'm not in need of money now.
The thing is,
I've found myself a powerful patron.
With a good patron comes good benefits.
If I am to achieve benefits,
I have to do my patron's bidding, right?
Be honest with me.
Who's really behind you?
The person behind me
holds tremendous power.
Ma Jin
thrived in Hanzhou
and always got his way.
You think
that was because of his abilities?
No.
His success was attributed
to this big shot behind me.
Hanzhang,
you're a director now.
Would you like to climb even higher up
the career ladder?
You don't want to move forward?
But I do.
I believe
I can still rise to a higher position.
I know.
Peng Hanzhang, in your eyes,
I'm just a doofus.
But now,
I'm done being a doofus.
I am He Muzhi.
Through my own efforts,
I will have everyone in Hanzhou
who sees me respectfully call me
"Mr. He."
Mr. He,
what exactly do you want me to do for you?
It's actually a simple task.
That officer named Qin Feng in your bureau
is a real pain in the neck.
He has always been after me.
It's getting on my nerves.
My boss is also very upset about it.
Just get him out of the way.
It's a small favor.
You'll do it for me, right?
After it's done,
I'll gain a foothold,
and you'll get a promotion.
What do you think?
[Legal Representative: Qiao Defu]
[Legal Representative: Liu Tianye]
Pleasure working with you.
Let's leave the rest to them.
Mr. Qiao,
I've booked a table at a restaurant
for a seafood dinner.
Shall we go celebrate?
Absolutely.
I happen to have arranged a party.
You should attend it.
Isn't it a bit inappropriate?
What's inappropriate about it?
Just friends hanging out.
Do you play cards?
A little.
Let me you take to a great place,
where we'll have a little game for fun.
What a big yacht.
Mr. Qiao, do you
often come here?
Not really.
Mr. He owns this place.
I brought you here for a visit.
Please.
After you.
It's Uncle Tianye?
Mr. Qiao.
Allow me to introduce...
Tianye?
What a surprise to see you here today.
You already know each other?
Yes, we do.
We interacted a lot back in the day.
With his business growing
bigger and bigger now,
he never hangs with me anymore.
Then we must have a good game tonight.
Sure!
Come on in, please.
Tianye, come on in.
This way, Mr. Qiao.
What on earth is going on
between Longwan Logistics and Qiao Defu?
First it was the Grand Paradise,
and now this.
What's Uncle Tianye up to?
Captain Qin,
what's your opinion?
I think now is too soon
to jump to conclusions.
What's happening on the yacht
is not clear yet.
What if it's just a business meeting?
Yeah.
We came here today
just to gather information.
Time to go back.
Let's figure things out first.
It's your turn.
Make a move.
I'll pass.
Let's wait for Mr. Qiao's choice.
Aren't you...
laying an ambush?
Well, I've got a low hand.
I'd rather not take risks,
considering the high stakes.
Don't you love taking risks best?
Mr. Qiao,
let me tell you.
Tianye is the top smuggler in Hanzhou.
He makes money by risking his life.
But every penny I present
is guaranteed to be clean.
Listen,
I'm not interested in your past.
As long as the pay's good,
anyone can be my partner.
That's right, Mr. Qiao.
Why not consider working with us?
We also rank top in Hanzhou
in terms of strength.
Plus,
the risk is lower.
Sorry.
Mr. He,
I've agreed to partner with Mr. Liu.
There are always
cooperation opportunities in business.
We'll work together
next time, okay?
Sure, okay.
Mr. He,
calculate how much I owe you.
I'd like to settle the account today.
What's that for?
It's not much money.
Let's just play.
Fun is all that matters.
Show your cards.
No need.
I'll pass.
Mr. Qiao is right.
Anyone can be a business partner.
I'll follow Mr. Qiao's example and pass.
What about you, Muzhi?
Impressive, Mr. He.
Going all in without looking at the cards.
Don't you fear my ambush?
I guess you have a terrible hand.
I've gone all in. Do you dare to call?
What if you have a worse hand than mine?
Why wouldn't I dare to call?
This is getting interesting.
Tension's building up.
I'm out of luck today.
Had better head out.
If Mr. Qiao is quitting, I'm quitting too.
I need some fresh air.
Mr. Qiao, I'll go with you!
I have three Aces.
How are you going to beat me?
Well,
I always make the best of a bad hand.
What if I get a straight flush?
A pause, please.
These petty stakes are boring me.
What kind of wager would you like?
Don't you enjoy gambling with your life?
Bring it on then.
Perhaps
heaven is on my side.
Turn the card over.
Liu Tianye.
Chances are that heaven's on your side,
but whether you get to see
this card tonight...
is up to me.
He Biao...
has basically laid his cards on the table
with Qiao Defu.
Maybe he'll even get one step ahead of us.
He's not much of a...
prominent businessman.
Things won't get that serious, right?
Besides,
Qiao Defu seems to have
powerful connections.
Could He Biao have him
under his thumb
after just a few card games?
Qiao Defu is insatiable.
All that money we've invested
might go down the drain.
Tianye.
He Biao is a strong rival.
He's capable of anything.
If necessary, we'll fight him.
Should he ruin our plans,
we'll ruin his as well.
It's between them and us
for the chance to make a quantum leap.
Keep close watch on everything.
We're close to success. Don't blow it.
What are you going to do?
I'd like to invite Su to dinner.
Okay. I'll arrange it.
Feng, you're here?
I see everyone's around.
Feng.
Have you eaten yet?
Yes.
Have you?
Here you are.
I already have a cup.
What are you two doing?
How's your company
doing?
All good.
Let me know if you have any problems.
Seriously?
Can you fix problems for us?
Of course.
Nowadays only family can help you.
Are outsiders even reliable?
Well, I know that.
What I mean is,
we'd hate to cause you trouble,
given the nature of your job.
T-There's a question
I have to ask you, Tianye.
Ask away.
Are you a gambler now?
No.
No?
Where did you go today?
I attended a business meeting
on a yacht today.
Why do you ask?
Have you been stalking me?
Stalking you?
I'm just asking.
Why would I stalk you?
So you were on a yacht?
Yes. And?
Was there a gambling table?
No.
That's good.
Tianye, take my advice—
I might as well say it to all of you.
Longwan Logistics
is getting off the ground.
Your lives are becoming better off.
You must stay away from gambling.
No fortune can survive
a gambling addiction.
You got it?
I already told you I didn't gamble.
Qiao Defu took me there
for a business meeting.
I was also surprised.
I already attended the meeting.
What's there to do about it?
I couldn't have just quit, right?
If they invite you to a yacht again
where there's a gambling table,
just give me a call.
I'll show you how fast we can respond.
I don't hope to arrest you guys
on a mission
to crack down illegal dens one day.
Arrest whom?
Do you have to act like a cop
all the time?
You're at home, not in the police station.
You treat us like this every day...
Alright.
You're not a gambler.
That's perfect.
I'm just reminding you to avoid
being taken advantage of.
No...
By the way, Tianye,
didn't I tell you to stay away
from He Gang and his fellows?
They run illegal businesses.
I'm a businessman, okay?
I had no choice.
Qiao Defu took me to meet He Biao.
I didn't initiate a meeting with him.
Do you have to do business
with these people?
I have to making a living, don't I?
By earning dirty money?
Can't you shift your focus of business?
Look, with the current team we have...
Let me put it this way.
They're engaged in shady business, right?
If you hang out with them
and they get caught one day
with you being at the scene,
won't you be taken by the police
for questioning too?
How will you explain yourself?
I'm clean. I'll have
a legit explanation for everything.
Alright?
You'll be detained anyway!
Look,
it'll be all fine as long as I'm clean,
right?
You just can't do business without them.
Is that so?
Is this an assault, officer?
What?
-You're a cop. Did you just assault me?
-What's going on?
Are you actually fighting?
No.
He accused me of assaulting him.
How's that possible?
Alright. Dismissed, everyone.
The baby is getting sleepy.
Tianye, hold him.
Baoying!
Look at me.
Don't touch him.
You just hit me again!
Tianfei!
You left your lighter there again.
Oh, I forgot it.
Tell me.
What happened just now?
Why did you quarrel
with Feng?
It wasn't a quarrel.
It really wasn't.
Aren't we now doing business
with Qiao Defu?
He's likely acquainted with bad people.
Feng worried that I might get scammed,
so he gave me a little reminder.
Wasn't he just looking out for you?
I knew he was.
So I didn't quarrel with him.
There are certain motions to go through
in doing business.
But Feng sees things in black and white.
How am I supposed to do business that way?
Listen, son.
Those motions in business aside,
you need to be clear
who truly cares about you
and who's secretly plotting against you.
You must figure that out, right?
Right. You've been telling me that
since childhood. I understand.
Okay. Then why did you
-get in a fight with Feng over this?
-I didn't. He raised his voice.
He was being all stubborn.
Mom,
how come you're getting
more and more grey hair lately?
How about I take you out to get it dyed?
I'm getting old.
Of course
more and more of my hair is going grey.
I won't dye it.
The grey can't be concealed anyway.
Just have your hair dyed. How about red?
It's trendy.
Your skin will look fairer that way.
Or purple.
They both represent prosperity.
Purple is no good.
That's a bit over the top.
-Won't I look terrible with purple hair?
-Red hair looks great.
Don't give in to aging, okay?
Longwan Logistics needs your leadership.
Mom, the sweet soup is ready.
Fancy a bowl of it?
Let me serve it.
I mean it, Mom.
Trust me and give it a try.
Dye your hair dark red.
It isn't noticeable indoors.
Only in sunlight
does it show a subtle red tint.
It's very stylish.
I'll pass.
See, there's no way
to conceal my grey hair.
Fine. Then let's buy a wig.
Wigs nowadays are made very well.
They're indistinguishable from real hair.
You can have a new hairstyle every day.
That means a different mood every day.
Fine. I'll listen to you.
Let's go try on wigs sometime.
Sure.
I'll make an appointment for you.
Okay.
What happened
between you and Tianye earlier?
What were you fighting about?
We weren't fighting.
We were just fooling around.
I saw everything.
Why hide it from me?
What am I hiding from you?
Has Tianye been close
with Qiao Defu lately?
Yes, as they're business partners now.
You two fought over that?
No, I'm just asking.
Distance yourselves from that rough crowd.
Take small steps in doing business.
Don't try to bite off
more than you can chew.
It could lead to trouble.
Tianye literally gave his all
to close this deal.
He racked his brains to become
Mr. Qiao's partner.
He even took loans from many people.
It was really hard.
Can't Tianye choose someone else?
Why must it be Qiao Defu?
So far, Mr. Qiao is our only option.
If this project proves to be a success,
Longwan Logistics will expand
beyond its borders.
Don't aim too high.
Take it slow.
Keep an eye on everything.
Don't worry.
I'll take good care of the family.
Just focus on your job
and care for yourself.
I'm not worried about you.
I'm worried about Tianye,
as he might
make hasty decisions.
All will be too late if that happens.
Don't worry.
I'll watch him.
Has Tianye gone to bed?
You wash the bowls.
Are you done eating?
Yes.
What would you like to eat?
Anything is fine.
Okay.
How come that guy looks so familiar?
He's that delivery guy from Longwan.
Hey, you.
What are you looking at?
Don't you know who I am?
Is everyone in Longwan
as proud as you are?
You know what?
Even Liu Tianye has to
respect me like I'm his father.
Look at me!
Smile and call me Mr. He!
-Call me Mr. He!
-Gang!
Gang,
what a coincidence.
What's going on?
Who are you to chime in?
Are you into this pretty boy?
Xiaomei,
you're an employee of the Grand Paradise.
Standing up for a lowly delivery guy...
Isn't it beneath you?
Gang,
do me a favor
and spare this delivery guy.
Fine.
I'll do you a favor then.
Give it to me.
Buddy,
if you drink up
this bottle of liquor
in front of your woman,
I'll let you go.
Okay?
Gang,
let me drink it.
It's just the same.
You wretch!
Did I ask you to drink it?
Fine!
Down it!
You love to drink, huh?
Now you have a chance!
Run!
Are you okay?
Are you okay, Gang?
Sorry.
I got you in trouble.
No worries.
I was thinking about resigning anyway.
Can I ask you something?
Go ahead.
Never mind.
Did you want to ask
why I got into this line of business?
It's not a forbidden question.
Although this doesn't
sound like a decent job,
I absolutely won't do
anything beyond my moral boundaries.
If you're in urgent need of money,
I have some to spare.
I'm not,
but my family is—
as if there's a bottomless pit to fill.
I understand.
I'm not rich
or powerful now.
But I swear to you,
as long as I'm alive
and breathing,
I won't let anyone hurt you again.
Tianye.
Come eat.
Have Mom and Ziyi finished eating?
They're with Baoying now.
Did Crazy just leave?
Have you two made up yet?
Nothing serious happened.
You all are just overreacting.
Do you know Zhang Xin,
an alumnus of yours?
Zhang Xin?
You mean the one working for Xinrui Group?
I know her, kind of.
She was quite famous back in college.
I ran into her a few days ago.
She asked about
our cooperation with Chengjian Group
and congratulated us.
I was wondering
how she got to know that
before we announced it.
What else did she say to you?
Well...
Nothing much.
She invited me to her horse ranch.
You should go.
Won't that be nice?
I don't know how to ride horses.
I'm just not interested.
You see,
Xinrui is a leading enterprise in Hanzhou.
She's your alumnus.
Why not use it to bond with her?
Longwan Logistics is developing.
What if there's a chance to collaborate?
It makes sense.
I'll do it.
That's the spirit.
I'll contact her later for a visit.
Make it quick.
You're doing great.
To the left. Perfect.
Good job.
Impressive.
Excellent.
I was a bit scared
when I first started riding a horse.
Don't be nervous.
Horses can sense it.
The more relaxed you are,
the more they trust you.
I remember all the tips on the ground,
but they slip my mind
when I'm on horseback.
You'll get better with practice.
Come here more often.
I'll teach you.
Longwan Logistics
will be a famous enterprise in Hanzhou.
Our company is just getting started.
We lag far behind Xinrui.
Aren't enterprises all built up
step by step?
That's true.
Though Longwan Logistics
is in its early stages,
we do have
our own advantages.
Whatever our focus is,
be it farming in the past
or logistics at present,
we've always prioritized integrity
in doing business.
I believe
Longwan Logistics
will be better and better.
I look forward
to hearing your advice, Xin.
There's a lot I need to learn from you.
Longwan Logistics
welcomes any support you may offer.
It hasn't been easy
for it to get where it is today.
Every opportunity will be cherished.
With you at Longwan Logistics,
it'll rise to prominence.
Then I'll often come ride horses with you.
I hope it won't bother you.
You're welcome anytime.
It's still early.
Let's go for another ride.
-Let’s go.
-Sure.
[Bao Fu Pawn Shop]
Well...
That's quite a large amount.
I know about him.
He's famous.
Who wouldn't have heard about him?
Alright, I got it. Don't worry.
Give me the car keys. I need to go out.
Give me the car keys.
I'm heading out for an issue.
Did He Biao give you a task?
Don't be so nosy.
Car keys.
Just take me with you.
You shouldn't be involved in this.
I can handle it myself.
Well, then,
tell me
who's He Biao's patron,
and I'll be gone.
Mai,
can you stop thinking about that thing
all day long?
I'll give you money if you want it.
All I need is a figure.
Just don't ask me about that thing again,
okay?
You think that'll make me quit?
I won't unless I'm dead.
Don't say that word, you stubborn guy.
Stop asking about it,
or this matter will cost you
your life one day.
Understood?
I'm not dead yet, am I?
I must keep probing as long as I'm alive.
Right?
I'll go with you.
I'm older than you, aren't I?
Will you listen to me just this once?
Go back and have tea.
I'll drive for you.
If you have a death wish,
don't die near me.
Do it somewhere else.
Mai, stop following me,
or our friendship's over.
Get lost!
Mai.
Crazy,
Su Hongbao is likely to make a move soon.
Okay. Got it.
We'll track him.
Okay.